http://www.agacgfm.org/about/privacy-policy.aspx

This site uses cookies to store information on your computer.
Some are essential to make our site work; others help us improve the
user experience. By using the site, you consent to the placement of
these cookies.
Please read our privacy policy
to learn more.
Learn about AGA
Who is AGA?
CGFM Certification
What is CGFM?
Employers
Why Hire a CGFM?
In-person/Virtual Training
Financial Systems Summit (FSS)
National Leadership Training (NLT)
ERM Workshop
PIO/CFO Summit
Professional Development Training (PDT)
Corporate Partners
Corporate Partner Advisory Group (CPAG)
AGA National Treasurers
This site uses cookies to store information on your computer. Some are essential to make our site work; others help us improve
your user experience. By using the site, you consent to the placement of these cookies. Please read our
privacy policy to learn more.
Search for:
About AGA
Chapters
Access AGA’s COVID-19 Resource Exchange
Membership
Renew Your Membership Today!
Learn About AGA
Who is AGA?Member BenefitsMembership TypesJoin or RenewFAQs
Connect
Awards & RecognitionGovernment Careers InformationMember DirectoryStudentsYoung ProfessionalsRecruit a MemberBoards & CommitteesCGFM Certification
Learn more about CGFM!
Candidates
My Path to CGFMCGFM ProcessPreparing for ExamsScheduling Your ExamsWork Verification FormCandidate FAQs
CGFMs
My CGFMDigital BadgeMaintaining CertificationCPE RequirementsRenew Your CGFMCGFM FAQs
Employers
Why Hire a CGFM?Verify CGFM StatusSchedule Group CGFM TrainingTraining & Events
View the event calendar
Print your CPE Certificate
In-person/Virtual Training
COVID-19 InformationAGA Virtual Breakfast & WebinarNational Leadership Training (NLT)PIO/CFO SummitERM WorkshopRPA WorkshopProfessional Development Training (PDT)Internal Control & Fraud Prevention TrainingTechnology & Transformation Summit (TTS)On-site CoursesCGFM Intensive Review Course
Virtual Training
WebinarsJournal CPE QuizzesSelf-Learning TrainingBecker Professional EducationCGFM Online CoursesResearch & Publications
2019 Annual CFO Survey
Journal of Government Financial Management
Read the Latest JournalEditorial CalendarSubmission GuidelinesAdvertiseOnline Journal Quizzes
Online Library
Executive ReportsIntergovernmental ReportsResearch ReportsSurvey SeriesStandards & Guidance
Citizen-Centric Reporting
Certificate of Excellence in Accountability Reporting
Financial Management Standards Board
Recent Guidance
Tools & Resources
COVID-19 Resource Exchange
Accountability Talks Podcast
intergov
Cybersecurity Hub
ERM Hub
Corporate Partners
About the Corporate Partner Advisory Group (CPAG)
CPAG Benefits
CPAG Calendar
CPAG Committees
CPAG Directory
CPAG Members
Research Sponsorship
Advertisers & Sponsors
Privacy Policy
Purpose
This privacy policy covers the privacy practices of the Association of Government Accountants (AGA) with respect to personally identifiable information (PII) that is transmitted electronically to or collected by AGA through this website, as well as collection of information through cookies and web beacons . The policy addresses the following items:
How AGA collects and uses PII.
With whom AGA may share PII.
The choices available to you, as a website visitor, regarding the collection, use and sharing of PII.
The security procedures AGA has in place for PII under our control.
AGA website cookie policy.
By visiting this website and/or using the website’s services, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. As we update and expand our services, this privacy policy may change. Be sure to check back to this page from time to time.
This website, located at www.agacgfm.org, including any services and features available on or through the website, such as blogs and user communities, is published and maintained by the association. AGA is referred to in this privacy policy as “we,” “us,” “our,” or other similar pronouns.
What is Personally Identifiable Information?
PII is any information about an individual that is maintained by an organization. PII includes information that can be used to distinguish or trace an individual’s identity, such as name, social security number, date and place of birth, mother’s maiden name, or biometric records. It also includes any other information that is linked or linkable to an individual, such as medical, educational, financial and employment information.
PII Collection
AGA does not collect PII from you unless you expressly volunteer the information. This includes instances when you:
Register for a meeting, become a member, register for certification, purchase or download an AGA product or service.
Request information (electronically) about AGA’s products and services, subscribe to newsletters, or enter a promotional contest.
Use or participate in various services or features made available on the website, including, for example and without limitation, blogs and other user communities.
Use various tools to select AGA products and services suitable for your website visit.
Request contact with an AGA representative.
Provide AGA with comments, questions or feedback about AGA products and services or your website experience.
PII Usage
AGA does not sell, rent, give away or loan any PII about its members and customers to any third party, other than organizations directly connected to AGA, including business partners. Organizations with access to PII are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this privacy policy.
Among other things, we may use your PII to:
Respond to your requests and inquiries.
Provide you with services and features offered on or through the website.
Communicate timely information and special offers (such as in emails, mailings and the like) about products, services, companies and events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you.
You may choose not to receive such information by managing your subscriptions at www.agacgfm.org/profile or by e-mailing agamembers@agacgfm.org. Please understand that if you choose not to receive promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us.
Credit Cards
If you register for a meeting or pay for products and services using a credit card, PII (such as your name and shipping address) and financial information (such as your credit card number and expiration date) may be required. This information may be used for billing purposes and to fill orders.
If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information may be used to get in touch with you. We also may share attendee registration information with exhibitors and sponsors of AGA conferences and similar events, which these exhibitors and sponsors may use to promote their products and services.
CGFM
If you become a Certified Government Financial Manager (CGFM), your name will be published on this website unless you expressly request its removal.
Marketing
The PII you give us through the website and information about your order may be combined with other PII (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. This information may be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient, and will help us to improve the operations and maintenance of our website and business.
Links
AGA’s website contains links to other sites. Some are links to the sites of AGA’s partners that offer AGA members and customers a variety of special products and services. Please be aware AGA is not responsible for the content, security or privacy practices on or of these other sites. We trust that you are aware of this when you leave the AGA website, and we encourage you to read the privacy statements of each site to which ours is linked.
This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by or on the website.
Security
This website takes reasonable precautions to protect PII submitted to AGA through its website. However, because the internet is an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. When possible, certain sensitive PII is encrypted and protected using SSL software.
You may be able to create an account on our website with a username and password. If so, you are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality and security of your account password, and you are responsible for any access to or use of the website through your password or account, whether such access or use has been authorized by you or on behalf of you, and whether such person or entity is your employee or agent. You agree to (a) immediately notify AGA of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security and (b) ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. When you desire to cancel your account on this website, it is your responsibility to notify AGA. We will not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this provision.
In the unlikely event that we believe the security of your PII in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances. If we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. You consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification. If you prefer we use another method to notify you in this situation, please e-mail us at agamembers@agacgfm.org with the alternative contact information.
If you have any questions about privacy on the AGA website, please email agamembers@agacgfm.org.
Correcting and Updating Personal Information
If your PII changes, such as a zip code, or if you no longer desire to use or access our website or services, log in to www.agacgfm.org/profile or send an email to agamembers@agacgfm.org or call AGA Customer Service at 800.AGA.7211 so we can correct, update or remove your PII, as requested. AGA members and customers can also access and update PII by logging into the password-protected area of the site.
Cookies and Web Beacons
In order to help enhance the performance and functionality of this website, we utilize session, persistent and third-party “cookies” that store a small piece of data on a users’ computers and collect certain information about the users’ visit to our website. We also use cookies to understand users’ browsing and buying activities so that we can measure the success of online advertising campaigns we run on the site. Our website also uses web beacons (either directly or from our partners), along with cookies, to determine if a user has visited a particular website. These beacons aid in providing more relevant advertising to the user, as well measuring the success of an advertising campaign, but provide no personally identifiable information.
Cookies are small text files that web servers typically send to users’ computer when they visit a website. Cookies are stored as text files on users’ hard drive, and can be accessed by web servers when the user visits a website or views an advertisement. A session cookie is a cookie that stores information as a user is using the website but is deleted once the browser session is finished. A persistent cookie is a cookie that stores information as a user utilizes the website and stores and uses that information in connection with future visits of the user to the website. Third-party cookies and/or web beacons are cookies or web beacons provided by our technology and/or advertising partners. Any third-party cookie or web beacon that we authorize for use on the website only collects that information described below for the same stated purposes as if we were directly collecting the information. For a third-party cookie or web beacon, the third-party will have access to the collected information in order to provide us with information or services to enhance the performance and functionality of the website.
The cookies and web beacons we use collect non-personally identifiable information about users of this website, including: browser used to access the site, date and time, the URL of the page being loaded, users who have visited a particular website(s), any previously assigned cookie identification (a unique identifier assigned to a user to identify repeat visitors), browser window size, the geographic location of the user, device and operating system used to access the website. The information we collect from these cookies and web beacons is used to determine information about a user’s visit to our website, including the number of visits, average time spent, pages viewed, navigation history through the website, and other statistics. This information is used to enhance the users experience while visiting our website and to improve the performance of our site by, among other things, allowing us to monitor site performance, making the site easier to use, measuring the effectiveness of promotional placements, and tailoring the site (including the ads and offers a user receives) to better match a user’s interests and preferences.
Users who prefer not to accept cookies can set their Internet browser to notify them when they receive a cookie or to prevent cookies from being placed on their hard drive. If you consent to our collection of cookies and you subsequently wish to withdraw your consent, you will need to manage the settings on your web browser to delete all cookies and disallow further acceptance of cookies. Please note that disabling cookies on your browser will prevent us from tracking your activities in relations to our website, however, it may also disable some of the functions and features of the site and the website may not work properly.
If you would like to determine your consent status, please contact us at: agamembers@agacgfm.org.
By continuing to use our website, you are agreeing to our placing cookies and/or web beacons on your computer in order to analyze the way you use our website. Please read this cookie policy carefully for more details about the information we collect when you use the website.
If you do not wish to accept cookies or web beacons in connection with your use of this website, please discontinue use of the website.
Notification of Changes
If AGA decides to change this privacy policy, we will post changes in the Privacy Policy section accessible from our home page so that you remain aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Any changes or updates will be effective upon posting. Under certain circumstances, we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our privacy policy by additional means, such as an email or a notice on the front page of our website.
Problems or Complaints
If you believe a violation of this privacy policy occurred, please contact agamembers@agacgfm.org. We will investigate, take appropriate action, and report back to you.
About AGA
Code of EthicsPressDonatePrivacy Policy
Contact Us
AGA National OfficeBecome a MemberBecome a CGFMDonate to AGA
Connect
Facebook Twitter LinkedIn Flickr
My AGA
My Upcoming EventsChapter ResourcesFREE Archived Recordings
Copyright © 2020, Association of Government Accountants. AGA® is a registered trademark.
